Everyone, I've been trying to record this video for a couple of days, but it's been
an emotional struggle to do that just with all of the labor that it takes, but
hope you can be patient with me. I want to start with sharing a little bit of my story
for those of you who don't know. I was born in Umdraman, Sudan
during Bashir's regime and during the Second Civil War. At the age of 4 or 5, I was a refugee,
and we weren't able to secure a permanent home until I was 11 turning 12. The early childhood
experience of being a child of war, being a refugee, being an asylum seeker has definitely
shaped who I am and how I show up. Now, a couple of days ago, the IRC released its 2024 watch
list of emergencies going on around the world, and it ranked them based off of the current
level of devastation and the projected level of devastation.
And topping the list, ranking in number one is my home, Sudan, where the majority of my
family currently lives. And then at the same time, I keep reading news of all of these large
scale, NGOs and IGOs, making cuts, stopping programs. And even with all of this, I'm not seeing us on
headline news. I'm not seeing us trending. I'm not seeing us being amplified. I know it's anti-black racism.
That's nothing new. It's quite expected. And it's quite devastating. Because the thing is,
well, me and those of us in the diaspora, as well as those of us still
locked in their homes because they're too afraid to go out in Sudan, even though they're starving,
even though they need basic essentials, we still somehow find a way to show up for everyone else.
And yet, no one shows up for black lives. We're there, we're there at the rallies, we're there at
the protests, we're there amplifying, we're there sharing, we're there carrying the burden of the labor
and doing the work. And yet, our struggles are still so invisible. And even when they do trend,
like 2020 George Floyd, as quickly as everyone comes to show up, they go away.
And I also wanted to share with all of you that on December 17th, we're going to be launching
Sudan Action Week. So myself and a few other Sudanese diaspora members and organizations
are coming together to not only give education, but also provide action plans.
And you'll find details in the caption on all of that. But the ask that I'm really making of all of you
show up for us the same way you showed up for every other cause. All of these struggles are
interconnected. And none of us can be truly free, if we are not all free.
So keep eyes on the genocides that are happening on the African continent. Keep eyes on Sudan, keep
eyes on Congo, keep eyes on Ethiopia, Tigray, keep eyes on black lives. Because to show up for everyone
and to have them not even know what's going on, when our devastation is ranked number one,
it burns the soul. It kills the soul. And the ask isn't to save. The ask is to amplify because we are
doing the work. But for some reason, anti-black racism, the reach isn't there. The support isn't there.
And so if you're not amplifying us, the media is not amplifying us. Social media isn't amplifying us.
Social media isn't anxious for you to spend more time oppressing us.
I'm working on local gefährstones.
When we're at public sitting there being some grease and 화장ping as an antique unit make sure